<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="app_name">TrustMe</string>
    <string name="menu_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="about_app_string">Yes – this app does exactly what you think! Trust Me gives you the power to make others trust you with the click of a button. Going into an interview, do you wish you could make your interviewer feel an instant connection and trust you? Going to an important business meeting and you need the other side to trust you and take you at your word? No problem. Just turn on Trust Me and leave it playing in the background. Trust Me gives you that extra “umph” you need to give those around you an instant feeling of confidence and trust in you. Anyone within range of you (about 30 to 60 feet) will get the vibe that you are someone to be trusted.\n
        \nTrust Me is completely idiot proof to use. You just push play. If you want the app to work in the background without ever stopping – push repeat. It doesn’t matter how loud or low your volume setting is. That’s it!\n
        \nBefore launching this app – we tested it out - vigorously. We had many beta testers that used the app and all reported that it absolutely made others trust them more. They reported that the effects were almost instantaneous.\n
        \nListen up! Trust Me wont let you get away with lying. The Trust Me app is not designed to override people’s basic senses and make them do whatever you want. But – Trust Me is absolutely the most powerful tool that you can use to make people near you instantly feel a sense of trust in you. Trust Me is about sending out the positive energy that makes people say, “I dunno. I just got a good vibe.” As with all of our enhanced social interaction apps, everyone – by using this app you are promising to use this app only for good – and never for evil!\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n</string>
    <string name="teliapp_string">TeliApp is an experienced mobile and enterprise applications company,
         harnessing the power of the iOS, Android, Windows and other mobile platforms. 
         In addition to building and deploying our own apps, we also offer B2B, B2C and Enterprise mobile applications solutions for companies of all sizes. 
         Our company is entirely US based - we do not outsource.\n\nTeliApp is building social apps, business apps, games, utilities and more. 
		Follow us @teliapp and like our Facebook Page to stay in touch and get the scoop on our exciting apps we have in the pipe. 
		Links to our social networking can be found at teliapp.com.</string>
    <string name="credits_string">Shabiba Hasan\nAlterrique Ingram\nChristina Kugel\nMark Kielinski\nLayla Lu\nIan Mathieson\nArman Shanjani\nJoshua Weiss</string>
    <string name="how_it_works_string">We developed Trust Me to help people get that extra something they need to instill a sense of trust in those around them. We all know that sight, smell and sound connect us to the world around us. \n\n
        Sight\nThe way a person looks or dresses can have an effect on whether you trust them or not. Maybe they look clean cut or particularly sharp and something about their polished appearance makes you trust them. Sometimes someone “just looks shady” and you can’t quite put your finger on why. \n\n
        Smell\nSmell plays a major role when it comes to trust. The smell of chemicals such as Oxytocin are known to have a intense effect on making others trust you.\n\n
        Sound\nA person’s voice can also have a profound effect on his or her ability to gain trust. Sometimes a person’s voice just inherently imbues a sense of trust, like Mr. Rogers or Morgan Freeman. Other times, it can have the opposite effect. That’s not by accident. It’s how our bodies work. Everybody’s senses are different.\n
        \nTrust Me works for you by using the power of sound to instill a sense of trust in those around you. Just like a person’s voice can imbue trust, so can certain sounds. These sounds don’t have to be able to be heard by your ears – just by your brain. You know how you can’t hear the sound of a dog whistle, but a dog can hear the dog whistle? Think of Trust Me like that. It’s not meant for your ears – it’s made for your brain. Certain sounds can actually affect the way your brain chemistry works, and Trust Me works on that level, behind the scenes, making others trust you. Like a secret weapon – just for you. \n
        \nIf you’re interested in all the science behind it, like our Facebook Page and read all about it! We didn’t want to stick pages and pages of sciency sounding stuff here.\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n</string>

</resources>